greetzap.com 2014-03-30

# GreetZAP

TimesMobile Ltd (TML) a wholly owned subsidiary of Times Internet Limited; located at http://in.indiatimes.com, is the mother brand of TML and powers/ manages the Online Properties (Brand Names) of the 'Times Group' interalia www.timesofindia.com, www.economictimes.com, www.navbharattimes.com, www.maharashtratimes.com including various internet sites and community boards and services, to name a few, (Indiatimes Channels) hereinafter collectively referred to as TML.

TML respects the privacy of its users and is committed to protect it in all respects. With a view to offer most enriching and holistic internet experience to its users TML offers a vast repository of Online Sites and variety of community services. You may read 'About Us' to know more about TML at www.timesmobile.in. Most of the Online Community Services are offered for free but you need a Universal mandatory registration to surf 'Indiatimes Channels' in detail. The information about the user as collected by TML is: (a) information supplied by users and (b) information automatically tracked while navigation (Information).

By using TML's website or its services, you consent to collection, storage, and use of the personal information you provide (including any changes thereto as provided by you) for any of the services that we offer.

**USER INFORMATION**

To avail certain sites/ services on our websites, users are required to provide certain information for the registration process namely: a) your name, b) email address, c) sex, d) age, e) PIN code, f) credit card or debit card details, g) medical records and history, h) sexual orientation, i) biometric information, j) password etc., and/ or your occupation, interests, and the like. The Information as supplied by the users enables us to improve our sites and provide you the most user-friendly experience. In some sites as in Indiatimes Contests, dating etc. we require your contact addresses.

All required information is service dependent and TML may use the above said User information to, maintain, protect, and improve its services (including advertising services) and for developing new services

Such information will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and accessible in the public domain or is furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force.

**COOKIES**

To improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users, TML may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the Identified Computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), TML will have no way of knowing who you are, even if TML assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply (an example of this is when you ask for our Personalised Horoscope). A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control.

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view). Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come.

**LINK TO THIRD PARTY SITES**

TML includes links to other websites. Such sites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond TML control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.

When we present information to our advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site.

When you register with TML, we may contact you from time to time about updation and upgrades of your content to provide the users such features that we believe may benefit you.

**INFORMATION SHARING**

TML shares the sensitive personal information to any third party without obtaining the prior consent of the User in the following limited circumstances:

a) When it is requested or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms; for complying with the applicable laws and regulations.

b) TML proposes to share such information within its group companies and officers and employees of such group companies for the purpose of processing personal information on its behalf. We also ensure that these recipients of such information agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**ACCESSING AND UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

When you use TML's websites, we make good faith efforts to provide you, as and when requested by you, with access to your personal information and shall further ensure that any personal information or sensitive personal data or information found to be inaccurate or deficient shall be corrected or amended as feasible, subject to any requirement for such personal information or sensitive personal data or information to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems. 

**INFORMATION SECURITY**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

All information gathered on TML is securely stored within the TML controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access.

However the internet is an ever evolving medium. We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Grievance Redressal**

Any complaints or concerns with regards to content or to report any abuse of laws or breach of these terms may be taken up with the designated grievance redressal officer as mentioned below via post or by sending an email to mobilecs@indiatimes.co.in or Mr. Sumit Chugh (“Grievance Redressal Officer”) 

Grievance Redressal Officer  
TimesMobile Limited   
Times Center, FC - 6, First Floor,  
Sector 16-A, Film City, Noida - 201301, India   
Ph: 0120 – 6636959

We request you to please provide the following information in your complaint:  
(a) Identification of the information provided by you   
(b) Clear statement as to whether the information is personal information or sensitive personal information   
(c) Your address, telephone number or e-mail address.   
(d) A statement that you have a good-faith belief that the information has been processed incorrectly or disclosed without authorization, as the case may be.   
(e) A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notice is accurate, and that the information being complained about belongs to you

**Facebook Policy**

**I. Features and Functionality**

1\. GreetZAP does not violate any law or the rights of any individual or entity, and does not expose Facebook or Facebook users to harm or legal liability as determined by Facebook in our sole discretion. In particular we (if applicable): comply with the Video Privacy Protection Act (VPPA), and obtain any opt-in consent necessary from users so that user data subject to the VPPA may be shared on Facebook. We represent that any disclosure to Facebook will not be incidental to the ordinary course of our business.   
2\. GreetZAP does not include functionality that proxies, requests or collects Facebook usernames or passwords.  
3\. GreetZAP does not circumvent (or claim to circumvent) our intended limitations on core Facebook features and functionality.   
4\. When we offer a service for a user that integrates user data into a physical product (such as a voice card), we only create a physical product for that user's personal and non-commercial use.   
5\. GreetZAP website offers an explicit "Log Out" option that also logs the user out of Facebook.  
6\. Special provision for apps on Pages: When a user visits our Page, if they have not given explicit permission by authorizing our Facebook app or directly providing information to our Page, we only use information obtained from Facebook and the user's interaction with our Page in connection with that Page.   
7\. GreetZAP does not use or make derivative use of Facebook icons, or use terms for Facebook features and functionality, if such use could confuse users into thinking that the reference is to Facebook features or functionality.   
8\. Reciprocity and Replicating core functionality:   
(a) Reciprocity: We enable people to easily share their experiences back with people on Facebook.   
(b) Replicating core functionality: We do not use Facebook Platform to promote, or to export user data to, a product or service that replicates a core Facebook product or service without our permission.   
9\. We do not include data obtained from Facebook in any search engine or directory without their written permission.

**II. Storing and Using Data You Receive From Us**

1\. GreetZAP only requests the data we need to operate our application.  
2\. GreetZAP may cache data that we receive through use of the Facebook API in order to improve our application’s user experience, but also try to keep the data up to date. This permission does not give us any rights to such data.   
3\. We have a privacy policy that tells users what user data we are going to use and how we will use, display, share, or transfer that data. In addition, we will include our privacy policy URL in the App Dashboard, and must also include a link to your app's privacy policy in any app marketplace that provides you with the functionality to do so.   
4\. Subject to certain restrictions, including on use and transfer, users give us their [basic account information](https://developers.facebook.com/policy/) when they with our application. For all other data obtained through use of the Facebook API, we obtain explicit consent from the user who provided the data to us before using it for any purpose other than displaying it back to the user on our application.   
5\. GreetZAP does not directly or indirectly transfer any data we receive from Facebook, including user data or Facebook User IDs, to (or use such data in connection with) any ad network, ad exchange, data broker, or other advertising or monetization related toolset, even if a user consents to such transfer or use. By indirectly we mean we cannot, for example, transfer data to a third party who then transfers the data to an ad network. By any data we mean all data obtained through use of the Facebook Platform (API, Social Plugins, etc.), including aggregate, anonymous or derivative data.   
6\. GreetZAP does not use Facebook User IDs for any purpose outside the application (e.g.,infrastructure, code, or services necessary to build and run application). Facebook User IDs may be used with external services that we use to build and run application, such as a web infrastructure service or a distributed computing platform, but only if those services are necessary to running application and the service has a contractual obligation with us to keep Facebook User IDs confidential.   
7\. In case we need an anonymous unique identifier to share outside application with third parties such as content partners, advertisers, or ad networks, we use our [mechanism](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/reference/api/user/). We do not ever share this anonymous unique identifier with a data broker, information broker, or any other service.   
8\. GreetZAP does not sell or purchase any data obtained from Facebook by anyone. Incase if we are acquired by or merge with a third party, we can continue to use user data within application, but we will not transfer data outside your application.   
9\. Incase if we stop using Platform or Facebook disables application, we will delete all information about a user we have received from Facebook unless: (a) it is basic account information; or (b) we have received explicit consent from the user to retain their data.   
10\. GreetZAP does not use a user’s friend list outside application, even if a user consents to such use, but we can use connections between users who have both connected to application.   
11\. GreetZAP will delete all data it receives from us concerning a user if the user asks us to do so, and will provide an easily accessible mechanism for users to make such a request. Facebook may require GreetZAP to delete data we receive from the Facebook API if we violate our terms.   
12\. GreetZAP does not include data received from Facebook concerning a user in any advertising creative, even if a user consents to such use.   
13\. GreetZAP does not give secret key and access tokens to another party, unless that party is an agent acting on our behalf as an operator of your application. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your account identifiers. 

**III. Content**

**A. General**

1\. Responsibility for content: GreetZAP is responsible for all content of and within application, including advertisements, user-generated content, and any content hosted, streamed or otherwise delivered to users by third parties. This content is not provided by Facebook. We also comply with the [ Facebook Community Standards.](https://www.facebook.com/communitystandards)  
2\. Demographic restrictions: GreetZAP is responsible for restricting access to content in accordance with content policies and all applicable laws and regulations. Please note that Facebook makes no representations regarding the sufficiency of any controls provided and that we are ultimately responsible for establishing legally compliant restrictions for each country where our app is visible.   
3\. Advertisements and cross-promotions:   
a. GreetZAP does not include advertisements, cross-promote other applications, or provide web search functionality in content distributed through [ Facebook social channels](https://developers.facebook.com/policy/).   
4\. Promotions: When we run, reference, or facilitate a promotion (contest, competition, or sweepstake) on Facebook, we comply with Facebook’s [ Promotions Guidelines](https://www.facebook.com/page_guidelines.php).   
5\. Permission from Facebook: We do not promote, or provide content referencing, facilitating, or containing online gambling, online real money games of skill or online lotteries without our written permission.   
6\. Quality of content: GreetZAP is responsible for providing users with a quality experience and must not confuse, defraud, mislead, spam or surprise users. For example, you must monitor your app's negative feedback in [ Application Insights](https://www.facebook.com/insights/) to ensure it stays below our thresholds, avoid excessive advertisements or bugs, and ensure the description of your app is consistent with your app's content. 

**B. Content Rights**

1\. GreetZAP does not promote or provide content that references, facilitates, contains or uses content that infringes upon the rights of any third party, including intellectual property rights, privacy, publicity, moral or other personal or proprietary rights, or that is deceptive or fraudulent.   
2\. GreetZAP ensures that we own or have secured all rights necessary to copy, display, distribute, deliver, render and publicly perform all content of or within application to Facebook users in all countries where we make the content available.   
3\. GreetZAP is responsible for all licensing, reporting and payout obligations to third parties required in connection with content of or within your application.   
4\. GreetZAP uses commercially reasonable geo-filtering technology to block access to application's content in countries where we are unauthorized to deliver such content, or where delivery of such content would otherwise infringe the rights of a third party.   
5\. Although we have no obligation to do so, in our sole discretion we may request, and you are required to provide us, proof that your application and any content of or within your application is properly licensed. 

**C. Third Party Content**

If your application contains content submitted or provided by third parties, you must comply with the following rules:

1\. In the United States you must take all steps required to fall within the applicable safe harbors of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act including designating an agent to receive notices of claimed infringement, instituting a repeat infringer termination policy and implementing a "notice and takedown" process. In other countries, you must comply with local copyright laws and implement an appropriate "notice and takedown" process upon receiving a notice of claimed infringement. 

**IV. Application Integration Points**

1\. GreetZAP does not incentivize users to use (or gate content behind the use of) [Facebook social channels](https://developers.facebook.com/policy/), or imply that an incentive is directly tied to the use of our channels.   
2\. GreetZAP does not pre-fill any of the fields associated with the following products, unless the user manually generated the content earlier in the workflow: Stream stories (user_message parameter for Facebook.streamPublish and FB.Connect.streamPublish, and message parameter for stream.publish), Photos (caption), Videos (description), Notes (title and content), Links (comment), and Jabber/XMPP.   
3\. If a user grants us a publishing [ permission](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/authentication/permissions/), actions we take on the user's behalf is expected by the user and consistent with the user's actions within app.   
4\. Platform integrations, including social plugins:   
a. Our advertisements does not include or be paired with any Platform integrations, including social plugins such as the Like button, without our written permission.   
b. GreetZAP does not sell or purchase placement of our [ Social Plugins](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/), and do not facilitate or participate in any like exchange program.   
c. GreetZAP does not incentivize users to Like any Page other than our own site or application, and any incentive we provide will be available to new and existing users who Like our Page.   
d. Ad networks, ad exchanges, and data brokers does not use Facebook’s Platform, logos, and trademarks (including, but not limited to, Platform APIs, social plugins, the Share button, and the F logo). 

**V. Enforcement**

Facebook can take enforcement action against GreetZAP and any or all of GreetZAP applications if Facebook determine in their sole judgment that our application violates Facebook Platform Terms and Policies. Enforcement action is both automated and manual, and can include disabling our application, restricting us and our application's access to Platform functionality, terminating agreements with us, or any other action as we in our sole discretion deem appropriate.
